<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<workzag-jobs>

    
        <position>
            <id>844793</id>
                                        <office>Norway - Oslo</office>
                                                    <recruitingCategory>Permanent Employee ENG</recruitingCategory>
            
            <name>Erlang/Elixir engineer</name>

                            <jobDescriptions>
                                                                    <jobDescription>
                            <name>The team and your role </name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                <p><em><span style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">As new license free spectrum is becoming available, there are a lot of new use cases that are opening up in the world and we are especially seeing an increase in the 5G, IoT and private network space. We in WGTWO want to cater our programmable network for these new and exciting use cases and we are currently actively exploring this area.</span></em></p><p><span style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">This means that we are also looking for more people to join our explorations!<br><br>We are now looking to welcome an experienced Erlang/Elixir engineer to continue to develop our platform with new key features. A background in telco systems is a plus, but not a requirement.</span></p><p><span style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">Most of our components are in-house developed in Java/Kotlin, Go, or Erlang, and are deployed on our self-managed Kubernetes cluster running on AWS. We are however language agnostic and believe in using the right tool for the job.</span></p><p><span style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;">We are firmly rooted in having people own their own work. This means that the team you will become a part of has a lot of freedom when it comes to planning and which features to build. At the same time the team is also responsible for operating the service once in production. We adhere to principles that include the use of continuous integration, continuous delivery, microservices and infrastructure as code.</span></p><p><span style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><strong>We believe you have experience with:</strong></span></p><ul><li style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><p>Writing code for distributed systems in Erlang or Elixir</p></li><li style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><p>A plus if you have worked on the design and development of one or several core network functions such as MME, SGW, PGW, AMF, UPF. </p></li><li style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><p>Building large scalable solutions</p></li><li style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><p>Caring about and shipping quality code</p></li><li style="font-size:14px;font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;"><p>Scalable containerized applications (Kubernetes or similar)</p></li></ul><p><span style="font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;font-size:14px;">The role is based in either of our offices in Trondheim, Stockholm or Oslo, but we are also open for remote colleagues. </span></p>
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                                                            <jobDescription>
                            <name>Our company culture</name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                <span style="font-family:Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;font-size:14px;">We’re a challenger in a well established multi-billion dollar industry. To succeed as a company, we need to deliver the high quality core services that subscribers are used to, while also adding value through the way that we operate. We believe our people and our culture will be a key differentiator in achieving this.<br><br>If you join us, you’ll get the trust and freedom needed to make a big impact in the telco industry. Since we’re solving telco problems in a modern way, we recruit from various industries and have people that used to work at Telenor, Google, Microsoft, and AWS. We promise that you’ll be surrounded by friendly, motivated and highly skilled coworkers. We have a culture of transparency and openness, and oftentimes we call ourselves a “start-up for grown-ups”. We know where we’re going, and with a lot of trust in each other, we’ll pave the way there together.<br><br>We’re a distributed company with offices in Oslo, Trondheim and Stockholm, as well as some remote colleagues in other locations (a total of 10 countries). We’ll pay for your phone and internet, as well as your lunch and office snacks. We’ll even pay you for your work! The Covid-19 pandemic forced a lot of companies to change how they think, but for us it confirmed that our remote-friendly and transparent approach goes a long way. We frequently host company wide activities online, like tech talks, demos, and failure fridays. We have Monday-kick offs, virtual lunches and fikas, and online gaming groups to keep the workday fun. Every year we also have a company wide off-site where we spend a whole week together share ideas and have fun. <br><br><strong>What's next?</strong><br>If you’re interested in working with us, please apply through the link below, or you can contact Marietta for any questions on marietta@wgtwo.com</span>
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                            </jobDescriptions>
            
                            <employmentType>permanent</employmentType>
            
                            <seniority>experienced</seniority>
            
                            <schedule>full-time</schedule>
            
                            <yearsOfExperience>5-7</yearsOfExperience>
            
            
                            <occupation>general_and_other_it_software</occupation>
            
                            <occupationCategory>it_software</occupationCategory>
            
                            <createdAt>2022-10-06T13:22:32+00:00</createdAt>
            
        </position>


    
        <position>
            <id>793432</id>
                                        <office>Norway - Trondheim</office>
                                        <department>Ecosystem</department>
                                        <recruitingCategory>Permanent Employee ENG</recruitingCategory>
            
            <name>Motivated Full-stack Developer</name>

                            <jobDescriptions>
                                                                    <jobDescription>
                            <name>The team and your role </name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                <p><br></p><p><strong>OUR VISION FOR THE FUTURE</strong></p><p>Up until now all mobile subscriptions have been the same, but we are changing this. People with a subscription from a Working Group Two powered mobile operator will soon enjoy a much richer set of features, and will be able to personalize their subscription by enabling products from our product marketplace. We will make this happen by enabling third party developers to create products that people love, and by helping operators distribute these products to their subscribers.</p><p>Our goal is to create a product ecosystem, which consists of three main components:</p><ul><li><p><strong>A developer portal:</strong> Enabling developers to use APIs and media streams for Messaging, Data, and Voice, and to submit their product to our marketplace. </p></li><li><p><strong>An operator marketplace:</strong> Allowing mobile operators to buy, manage, and distribute products to their subscribers.</p></li><li><p><strong>A subscriber marketplace:</strong> Letting mobile subscribers find, activate and launch the products they want to add to their subscription.</p></li></ul><br><p><strong>THE POSITION</strong></p><p>We’re looking for a fullstack developer preferably with product experience, to help us build our Developer Portal. The Developer Portal team currently consists of two other fullstack developers, a designer, a UX researcher, and a product owner. Your main responsibilities will be writing code and sparring with your coworkers. One of our current fullstack developers has a preference for frontend, so it would be good if you have a preference for backend.</p><p>Most of our projects use this stack:</p><pre>Figma
Vuetify ───╗
Vue        ║
REST       ║
gRPC       ║
Javalin    ║─── This position
Jetty      ║
Kotlin     ║
jOOQ       ║
SQL ───────╝
K8S
AWS</pre>You don’t have to know everything from Vuetify to SQL. Maybe you’ve worked with React instead of Vue, maybe you’re <br>familiar with Tomcat but not Jetty? Picking up Kotlin should be doable if you know Java or C#. It’s not expected that you <br>know our entire stack before you join, as long as you’re willing to learn (the stack might also change). <br>We do, however, expect you to have some web backend and database experience, and we expect you to work hard to <br>familiarize yourself with our stack and our projects.
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                                                            <jobDescription>
                            <name>Our company culture</name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                <p>We’re a challenger in a well established multi-billion dollar industry. To succeed as a company, we need to deliver the high quality core services that subscribers are used to, while also adding value through the way that we operate. We believe our <br>people and our culture will be a key differentiator in achieving this.</p><p>If you join us, you’ll get the trust and freedom needed to make a big impact in the telco industry. Since we’re solving telco problems in a modern way, we recruit from various industries. We have people that used to work at unknown startups, large <br>tech companies like Google, Spotify, and AWS, as well as telecoms like Telenor. We promise that you’ll be surrounded by <br>friendly, motivated and highly skilled coworkers. We have a culture of transparency and openness, and oftentimes we call <br>ourselves a “start-up for grown-ups”. We know where we’re going, and with a lot of trust in each other, we’ll pave the way <br>there together!</p>We’re a distributed company with offices in Oslo, Trondheim and Stockholm, hubs in Germany and Japan, as well as some <br>remote colleagues in other locations (a total of 10 countries). We’ll pay for your phone, internet and equipment, as well as <br>your lunch and office snacks. We’ll even pay you for your work! The Covid-19 pandemic forced a lot of companies to change how they think, but for us it confirmed that our remote-friendly and transparent approach goes a long way. We frequently <br>host company wide activities online, like tech talks and demos. The whole company also meets up once or twice per year, <br>and smaller groups meet more often. We also have Monday-kick offs and online gaming groups to keep the workday fun.<br><br><p>WHAT’S NEXT?</p><p>If you’re interested in working with us, please apply through the link below, or contact Theresa for any questions on </p><p>theresa@wgtwo.com. We’re looking forward to getting to know you! </p>
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                            </jobDescriptions>
            
                            <employmentType>permanent</employmentType>
            
                            <seniority>experienced</seniority>
            
                            <schedule>full-time</schedule>
            
                            <yearsOfExperience>5-7</yearsOfExperience>
            
                            <keywords>Fullstack, Javalin,Java,Vue,Kotlin</keywords>
            
                            <occupation>software_and_web_development</occupation>
            
                            <occupationCategory>it_software</occupationCategory>
            
                            <createdAt>2022-08-22T16:47:12+00:00</createdAt>
            
        </position>


    
        <position>
            <id>139167</id>
                                        <office>Sweden - Stockholm</office>
                                                    <recruitingCategory>Permanent Employee ENG</recruitingCategory>
            
            <name>Software Engineer</name>

                            <jobDescriptions>
                                                                    <jobDescription>
                            <name>The team and your role </name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                <p>We are now looking to welcome an experienced software engineer to join our office in Stockholm, and continue to develop our platform with new key features. </p><p>Most of our components are in-house developed in Java/Kotlin, Go, or Erlang, and are deployed on our self-managed Kubernetes cluster running on AWS. We are however language agnostic and believe in using the right tool for the job. </p><p>We are firmly rooted in having people own their own work. This means that you are allowed a lot of freedom when it comes to planning and which features to build. However, our engineers who develop the code are also responsible for operating the code once in production. We adhere to principles that include the use of continuous integration, continuous delivery, microservices and infrastructure as code. </p><p>We believe you have experience with: </p><ul><li><p>Writing distributed, well designed services in a JVM language such as Kotlin or Java, and at least one other programming language, such as Go, C#, C++, Erlang, Python, Rust or Javascript.</p></li><li><p>Building large scalable solutions. </p></li><li><p>Caring about and shipping quality code.</p></li><li><p>Scalable cloud services (AWS, or other cloud infrastructure providers). </p></li><li><p>It is an added bonus if you have knowledge of the telco industry, telco protocols, VoIP systems or know networking by heart, but it is not required.</p></li></ul>
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                                                            <jobDescription>
                            <name>Our company culture</name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                <p>We are challenging a well-established multi-billion dollar industry, and this is not a trivial task.  In order to do so, we need to continue delivering high-quality solutions on par with the existing standards, while embedding innovation in the way we operate and create value for the end-users. This is why we believe our people and culture is our key differentiator. </p><p>Joining us, you will get a lot of freedom and responsibility to create a big impact in the telco industry and you will be surrounded by friendly colleagues with high expertise. We have a culture of transparency and openness, and oftentimes we call ourselves a “start-up for grown-ups”. We know where we are going, and with a lot of trust in each other, we co-create the path to get there. </p><p>You will be part of a distributed team with main offices in Oslo, Trondheim and Stockholm as well as some remote colleagues in other locations. We believe in doing things together and that is why we frequently host company wide activities like tech talks, demos, and Failure Fridays. We also make sure everyone can get together at an offsite three times a year to have fun, discuss important topics and hack on crazy projects.</p><br>WHAT’S NEXT?<br>If you’re interested in working with us, please apply through the link below, or contact Theresa for any questions on theresa@wgtwo.com. We’re looking forward to getting to know you! 
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                            </jobDescriptions>
            
                            <employmentType>permanent</employmentType>
            
                            <seniority>experienced</seniority>
            
                            <schedule>full-time</schedule>
            
                            <yearsOfExperience>5-7</yearsOfExperience>
            
            
                            <occupation>systems_and_process_engineering</occupation>
            
                            <occupationCategory>engineering</occupationCategory>
            
                            <createdAt>2019-08-30T10:34:02+00:00</createdAt>
            
        </position>


    
        <position>
            <id>232715</id>
                                        <office>Sweden - Stockholm</office>
                                                    <recruitingCategory>Permanent Employee ENG</recruitingCategory>
            
            <name>Software engineer -Norway/Sweden/Remote - Europe</name>

                            <jobDescriptions>
                                                                    <jobDescription>
                            <name>The team and your role </name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                As new license free spectrum is becoming available, there are a lot of new use cases that are opening up in the world and we are especially seeing an increase in the 5G, IoT and private network space.<br>We, of course, also want to cater our programmable network for these new and exciting use cases and we are currently actively exploring this area.<br>This means that we are also looking for more people to join our explorations. We are now looking to welcome an experienced <strong>software engineer</strong> to join us and continue to develop our platform with new key features.<br><br>Most of our components are in-house developed in Java/Kotlin, Go, or Erlang, and are deployed on our self-managed Kubernetes cluster running on AWS. We are however language agnostic and believe in using the right tool for the job.<br>We are firmly rooted in having people own their own work. This means that you are allowed a lot of freedom when it comes to planning and which features to build. However, our engineers who develop the code are also responsible for operating the code once in production. We adhere to principles that include the use of continuous integration, continuous delivery, microservices and infrastructure as code.<br><br>We believe you have experience with:<br><ul><li>Writing distributed, well designed services in any of the languages C, C++, Go, Erlang or Java/Kotlin </li><li>Building large scalable solutions. </li><li>Caring about and shipping quality code.</li><li>Scalable cloud services (AWS, or other cloud infrastructure providers). </li><li>Prior telco industry experience is not required. </li></ul>The role is based in either of our offices in Stockholm, Oslo or Trondheim.
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                                                            <jobDescription>
                            <name>Our company culture</name>
                            <value>
<![CDATA[
                                We’re a challenger in a well established multi-billion dollar industry. To succeed as a company, we need to deliver the high quality core services that subscribers are used to, while also adding value through the way that we operate. We believe our people and our culture will be a key differentiator in achieving this.<br><br>If you join us, you’ll get the trust and freedom needed to make a big impact in the telco industry. Since we’re solving telco problems in a modern way, we recruit from various industries and have people that used to work at Telenor, Google, Microsoft, and AWS. We promise that you’ll be surrounded by friendly, motivated and highly skilled coworkers. We have a culture of transparency and openness, and oftentimes we call ourselves a “start-up for grown-ups”. We know where we’re going, and with a lot of trust in each other, we’ll pave the way there together.<br><br>We’re a distributed company with offices in Oslo, Trondheim and Stockholm, a hub in Germany, as well as some remote colleagues in other locations (a total of 8 countries). We’ll pay for your phone and internet, as well as your lunch and office snacks. The Covid-19 pandemic forced a lot of companies to change how they think, but for us it confirmed that our remote-friendly and transparent approach goes a long way. We frequently host company wide activities online, like tech talks, demos, and failure fridays. This year we’ve replaced our quarterly offsites with online HackDays. We also have Monday-kick offs, virtual lunches and fikas, and online gaming groups to keep the workday fun.
]]>
                            </value>
                        </jobDescription>
                                                            </jobDescriptions>
            
                            <employmentType>permanent</employmentType>
            
                            <seniority>experienced</seniority>
            
                            <schedule>full-time</schedule>
            
                            <yearsOfExperience>5-7</yearsOfExperience>
            
            
                            <occupation>software_and_system_architecture</occupation>
            
                            <occupationCategory>it_software</occupationCategory>
            
                            <createdAt>2020-07-14T10:47:44+00:00</createdAt>
            
        </position>


    
</workzag-jobs>
